<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder
        xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
        xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
        >
    <g:PopupPanel>
        <g:ScrollPanel ui:field="scrollPanel">
            <g:VerticalPanel>
                <g:HTMLPanel>
                    <h3>Where am I? Feature</h3>
                    <p>Clicking on the map will create a marker showing what imported features are associated with
                    the coordinates that were clicked on.</p>

                    <h3>Selecting Map Features</h3>
                    <p>Users can select a map and associated features via the "Features" Stack Panel. Note that borders
                        must be imported
                        from the Census Department before they can be displayed. Also, features must be imported from
                        the USGS before they
                        can be displayed on the map.
                    </p>

                    <p>The user must select which type of border they wish to view, then the state (and possibly county,
                        depending on the
                        border type). If not selecting to view a state or county, the user must select a specific item
                        they wish to view
                        from the Specific Item box.
                    </p>

                    <p>Next, the user has the option of selecting which type of USGS feature they wish to display within
                        the borders they
                        have selected. This is not mandatory. Currently, only one feature type at a time can be
                        displayed. These features
                        will be displayed as a Google Maps Marker, which can be clicked on for further information.
                    </p>
                    <h3>Export Functions</h3>

                    <p>Export functions are not currently implemented.</p>

                    <h3>Managing Borders, Features, and Administration</h3>

                    <p>To import or delete a border, click the Manage Borders button in the Admin tab of the
                    application stack panel. It is HIGHLY recommended that you import State and County features
                    before importing features based on them.</p>

                    <p>To import USGS features for a location, click the Manage Features, then select the state
                    to display the features for. Currently, all USGS feature types for the state will be imported.</p>

                    <p>To select the year of the TIGER/Line data used for displaying borders, or changing the date
                    of the USGS data set, click the App Settings button. Changing either of these items will
                    dump all data related to it (i.e. changing from 2010 to 2009 will dump all imported borders that
                    were created from the 2010 data). Also, the USGS dataset is updated about every 2-3 months,
                    and archives are not kept. To get the current version, visit http://geonames.usgs.gov/domestic/download_data.htm
                    and look for the last updated date.</p>
                </g:HTMLPanel>
                <g:HorizontalPanel>
                    <g:Button ui:field="closeButton">Close</g:Button>
                </g:HorizontalPanel>
            </g:VerticalPanel>
        </g:ScrollPanel>
    </g:PopupPanel>

</ui:UiBinder>